King of the Bingo Game is a drama film directed by Elise Robertson.
Harlem, 1943.
Sonny is a struggling African American who frequents the bingo parlor in a desperate
attempt to provide for his family in post-Depression era New York.
Sonny, played by Colman Domingo.
George, played by Bennie Lewis.
Leroy, played by Earl L. Robertson.
Woman Eating Peanuts, played by Rashida Clendening.
Film Noir Hero, played by Peter Macon.
Film Noir Female, played by Anika Noni Rose.
Richard Karn (born Richard Karn Wilson; February 17, 1956) is an
American actor, author and former game show host.
He starred as Al Borland in the ABC series Home Improvement
and as Fred Peters in the Hulu series Pen15.
Karn was also the fourth host of Family Feud from 2002 to 2006.
The film explores themes of bingo, racism, harlem,
new york city, 1940s, anti-blackness.
The tone is emotional.